[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ I'VE BEEN CHEATED BY YOU
SINCE I DON'T KNOW WHEN ♪
♪ SO I MADE UP MY MIND ♪
♪ IT MUST COME TO AN END ♪
♪ LOOK AT ME NOW,
WILL I EVER LEARN ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW HOW, BUT
I SUDDENLY LOSE CONTROL ♪
♪ THERE'S A FIRE
WITHIN MY SOUL ♪
♪ JUST ONE LOOK AND I
CAN HEAR A BELL RING ♪
♪ ONE MORE LOOK AND I
FORGET EVERYTHING, WHOA ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, HERE I GO AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, HOW CAN I RESIST YOU ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, DOES
IT SHOW AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, JUST HOW
MUCH I'VE MISSED YOU ♪
♪ YES, I'VE BEEN
BROKEN-HEARTED ♪
♪ BLUE SINCE THE DAY WE PARTED ♪
♪ WHY, WHY DID I
EVER LET YOU GO ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, NOW I REALLY KNOW ♪
♪ MY, MY, I COULD
NEVER LET YOU GO ♪
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ I'VE BEEN ANGRY AND SAD
ABOUT THINGS THAT YOU DO ♪
♪ I CAN'T COUNT ALL THE TIMES ♪
♪ THAT I'VE TOLD
YOU WE'RE THROUGH ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU GO, WHEN
YOU SLAM THE DOOR ♪
♪ I THINK YOU KNOW THAT YOU
WON'T BE AWAY TOO LONG ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THAT I'M
NOT THAT STRONG ♪
♪ JUST ONE LOOK AND I
CAN HEAR A BELL RING ♪
♪ ONE MORE LOOK AND I
FORGET EVERYTHING, WHOA ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, HERE I GO AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, HOW CAN I RESIST YOU ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, DOES
IT SHOW AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, JUST HOW
MUCH I'VE MISSED YOU ♪
♪ YES, I'VE BEEN
BROKEN-HEARTED ♪
♪ BLUE SINCE THE DAY WE PARTED ♪
♪ WHY, WHY DID I
EVER LET YOU GO ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, EVEN IF I SAY ♪
♪ BYE-BYE, LEAVE
ME NOW OR NEVER ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, IT'S
A GAME WE PLAY ♪
♪ BYE-BYE DOESN'T MEAN FOREVER ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, HERE I GO AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, HOW CAN I RESIST YOU ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, DOES
IT SHOW AGAIN ♪
♪ MY, MY, JUST HOW
MUCH I'VE MISSED YOU ♪
♪ YES, I'VE BEEN
BROKEN-HEARTED ♪
♪ BLUE SINCE THE DAY WE PARTED ♪
♪ WHY, WHY DID I
EVER LET YOU GO ♪
♪ MAMMA MIA, NOW I REALLY KNOW ♪
♪ MY, MY, I COULD
NEVER LET YOU GO ♪
[UPBEAT MUSIC]